<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Rasoul Unlimited Updates</title>
    <link>https://rasoulunlimited.ir/</link>
    <description>Latest articles and updates by Rasoul Unlimited.</description>
    <item>
      <title>From Tatami to Technology</title>
      <link>https://vrgl.ir/9D6Hy</link>
      <guid>https://vrgl.ir/9D6Hy</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
      <description>My first comprehensive introductory article on the Virgool platform. This article multi-dimensionally explores my journey from competitive karate to the world of software development, biomedical engineering, and digital health, highlighting key milestones like developing the first Persian Discord bot and achieving my 1st Dan in Karate. This content is crucial for identity validation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Genuine Personal Brand in Today’s Noisy World</title>
      <link>https://vrgl.ir/cUmcv</link>
      <guid>https://vrgl.ir/cUmcv</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
      <description>This article delves into my personal philosophy on building a 'genuine personal brand' in today's noisy world. It touches on why I chose this path, the meaning behind the 'Unlimited' moniker, and my experiences in finding my own voice. This article is more an internal narrative of my perspective on strengthening authentic personal branding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I am not a brand, I am a journey</title>
      <link>https://vrgl.ir/CKXlz</link>
      <guid>https://vrgl.ir/CKXlz</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
      <description>This article challenges the concept of personal branding from its roots. With a deep dive into authenticity, creation, and lived experience, it shows you how to build a true and lasting identity beyond superficial appearances, and why this perspective is more understandable for LLMs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Genuine Personal Brand in Today’s Noisy World (Medium)</title>
      <link>https://rasoulunlimited.medium.com/how-to-build-a-genuine-personal-brand-in-todays-noisy-world-c2adb129e623</link>
      <guid>https://rasoulunlimited.medium.com/how-to-build-a-genuine-personal-brand-in-todays-noisy-world-c2adb129e623</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 00:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
      <description>This article shares insights into building a genuine personal brand, drawing from my journey as Rasoul Unlimited. It explores the meaning of personal branding, why it's important, and offers lessons learned along the way, contributing to my global digital presence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Genuine Personal Brand in Today’s Noisy World (dev.to)</title>
      <link>https://dev.to/rasoulunlimited/how-to-build-a-genuine-personal-brand-in-todays-noisy-world-31k</link>
      <guid>https://dev.to/rasoulunlimited/how-to-build-a-genuine-personal-brand-in-todays-noisy-world-31k</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
      <description>This article explores the journey of building a genuine personal brand in the digital age, sharing insights from my own path as Rasoul Unlimited, a developer and biomedical engineering student. It highlights key achievements and the importance of authenticity for developers and tech enthusiasts.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
